hsmarket.com 2012-12-30

# HSMARKET - Web Directory- Privacy Policy

[Home](http://www.hsmarket.com/ "Browse to: Home") | Hsmarket Privacy Policy 

Hsmarket ([http://www.Hsmarket.com](http://www.hsmarket.com/)) considers Internet user privacy and data protection to be of paramount importance. Hsmarket complies with the Data Protection Act 1998 in relation to all processing of personal data supplied to us by users and other personal data in our possession for any reason. We have registered with and notified the Data Protection Commissioner of our practice affecting personal data. 

This statement discloses the privacy policy for the Hsmarket network of sites, which encompass the site http://www.hsmarket.com and all co-branded versions of this site that collectively form and are referred to as the Hsmarket network. This statement does not extend to sites that are linked to or which are not part of the Hsmarket network. 

**COOKIES**  
A 'cookie' is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on you computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. You can decide if you want to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser to either accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. 

The Hsmarket network uses cookies to assign identification to your individual browser. This identifies your browser – but not you – to our servers every time you visit our network. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. Unless you voluntarily advise us, the Hsmarket network will never know who you are, even though we assign your browser a cookie. 

The information gathered through the use of cookies, allows the Hsmarket network to offer a quality Internet service and easily accessible online content to our users, and catalogue traffic patterns throughout the network in a manner that provides personal privacy protection. 

We also keep track of your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information about you, such as your location and your Internet Service Provider. The Hsmarket network may also collect aggregate information on how our users are utilising the site. This might include information regarding traffic patterns through the sites. 

Other organisations that place advertising on our network also have the ability to assign a different cookie to your browser in a process that the Hsmarket network does not control. Again, unless you voluntarily advise them, these advertisers will also never know who you are. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
At specific times Hsmarket may ask you to provide us with personal information, including but not limited to your name and email address, in order for you to register for a service (e.g. My London Property Guide). You may choose not to provide us with this information; however, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service or offer you personalised content. 

Please note that all the information you provide to the Hsmarket network will be stored and processed in either the United Kingdom or Australia. 

Occasionally we will send you email communications to provide information, which we think you will find useful, including information about new products and services from the Hsmarket network. It is our policy only to send email to customers who give us permission to do so. Our site provides you with the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving communications from Hsmarket at the time we ask you for this information. In addition, whenever we contact you via email, we will also have instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future emails from us if you so choose. 

Other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising or content. The Hsmarket network does not control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers or content providers directly if you have any questions about their use of this information. Additionally, the Hsmarket network does not control the information collection and distribution policies on sites outside the Hsmarket network, although we do encourage our co-branding partners to adopt privacy policies similar to this one. 

**SHARING OF DATA**  
The Hsmarket network will not disclose any of your personal information to a third party without your consent, unless we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it or that the rights or property of the Hsmarket network need to be protected. 

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**  
The Hsmarket network contains links to other sites not affiliated with the Hsmarket network. These sites have their own policies and practices with respect to online privacy, and the Hsmarket network cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these unaffiliated websites. In addition, in certain instances, a Hsmarket advertiser may ask you for personal information. Hsmarket cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices of its advertisers; however, Hsmarket encourages our partners and advertisers to adopt privacy policies similar to our own. 

**COMMENT**  
We suggest that you practise reasonable discretion with any site when providing site operators/owners with personal information. It should also be noted that whenever you post personal information in publicly accessible places, such as chat rooms or message boards, this information becomes available to anyone with access to the Internet. Therefore, we recommend that you refrain from posting any information that you do not want seen in these public areas. You should feel free to contact any site that requests personal information from you if you have any questions regarding its policies.
